Nutchaphon Sitthiarsa

Full-stack developer



100/428 No.8, Sansai Sub-district, Muang District, Chiang Rai, 57000



093-6628926



ABOUT ME

Skilled Java developer and team leader with diverse experience utilizing Java tools for client-server environments and fluid understanding of many programming languages including C, C++, JavaScript, XML, and HTML. Worked with a large team of GUI and Java developers to maintain and improve company projects. Assisted with disaster recovery environments for critical business applications. Received the Eclipse Award for Best Java Application.

EDUCATION

Panyapiwat Institute of Management

08/2011 - 09/2015

Bachelor of Engineering: Computer Engineering

SKILLS

EXPERIENCE

G-Able Co., LTD

2023 - 2024

Software Tester

Tested functional and compatibility of new programs or updates in comparison to existing applications.

Optimized test cases to maximize success of manual software testing.

Supported test review, defect control and configuration management within delivery pipeline.

G-Able Co., LTD

2022 - 2023

Software Tester / Automate Tester

Tested functional and compatibility of new programs or updates in comparison to existing applications.

Optimized test cases to maximize success of manual software testing.

Supported test review, defect control and configuration management within delivery pipeline.

LANGUAGE

English

Fluently

HOBBIES



Travel



Music